all right what's up traders just had
somebody come in uh we're going to
i don't know if you can see in the
background here
there's a fireplace there ignore that
one and uh there's a fireplace there and
you can see the scratched up floors like
the cats
[__] destroy them we just had
somebody come in here kind of giving us
a rundown
of what we should do with the fireplace
and foreign
we're going to retile it all it was
summer because you guys know i am going
to be
moving to asia calm winter time uh so
we're moving out of here so we're gonna
have to make the place a little bit
nicer might as well do it in the summer
while we can and then enjoy it a little
bit um the
chimney there uh is over here um chimney
here
and that is gonna be much better to be
destroyed in the summer
so there's less rain leaking through the
ceiling
last week was such an amazing week so
we're starting off this week the sunday
trading already over
we didn't have any any trades go off
just a lot of ranging that day
but decided sun is coming out there's
going to be a lot of camping
a lot of drinking and such and
thinking because the training went so so
well
with the hermit moon we're going to
apply that to more aspects of our life
here
we're going to start doing the um the
domino effect
one small improvement creates a chain
reaction
and we're going to improve on another
thing so we're quitting drinking we're
going full health here
and hopefully if you guys want to join
along you can for the summer because
really
you don't really need you don't really
need it kind of got to the point where
um you know alcohol doesn't really
affect you too much anymore after you've
just been drinking so much because of
snowboarding and all these things right
so we're just having multiple beers
every day
it doesn't really do a whole lot anymore
um so we might as well just quit it
and um see how that affects the trading
game
so uh best of luck into this week let's
go into it
a little bit come on buddy what's that
so just got back from the gym and wanted
to just talk a little bit about psyche
um and uh the the effect on your
happiness there uh
is something that i sort of realized and
the reason why i'm quitting the drinking
here pretty much every freaking day
uh we were going out snowboarding and
just having a couple drinks it really
started to affect your psyche and
everything like that along with other
things going on in the trading world and
everything
and so it's very very difficult to keep
your happiness about you
and then you start grasping for things
that are external sources of happiness
and it's
not true happiness anymore so something
that i kind of realized on
a shroomy strip there uh the other day
you know my happiness was leaving and it
was starting to become
geared from or powered by external
sources of happiness which is not who i
am so we're getting back into meditation
we're quitting drinking there for
at least a long while and we're we're
just going more deeper into
kind of this just this pursuit for
being happy um just from regular
regular life little things and things
like that and then that in turn is going
to create a much
stronger trading environment uh and
you're going to be able to trade much
much better you guys want to make sure
that you're trading for the right reason
right you're not trading to
be making money right and that's
something i've really noticed over the
years
is if i'm trying to make money at any
point i'm gonna be
losing money i'm gonna be forcing things
and not going to be doing it properly
and then it's going to cause more
psychological damage
um really what you want to do is just
look to do the right action
every single time and then in turn the
money will follow that's all i kind of
wanted to say about that what i'm going
to do quickly here we're just going to
meditate here i could record that but
essentially it's just going to look like
this for you guys
so there you go take that image and
watch it forever however long you want
that's me meditating for the next 5-10
minutes
and then we're gonna go go get a haircut
and enjoy this beautiful day
so just snagged a bitcoin long
not sure how well you can see this one
took about half off here uh just because
i had to jump in the shower i'm about to
head out
um coming back the stop is now here
um still uh just on those lows there
took half off and then we're letting the
rest just run a little bit higher
hopefully it hits it that's bitcoin
there today i'm gonna make a crypto
trading course
how i invest in crypto how i buy certain
coins you know all the general crypto
stuff i'm gonna make a course and just
make it real cheap or something for you
guys like 100 bucks some [__] like this
and then you know a couple trading
strategies or something
but i'm gonna make that pretty soon here
probably this month gonna head out
and get a little bit of tan you can see
my skin's a bit white here
sun's coming out so i do need to get a
little bit tanned before i start getting
burnt
haven't been to a barber in like five
years i always go get ash to cut my hair
i'm so sh i gotta go run to her place
that's pretty much it for the week here
guys i got some snowboarding tomorrow
and then on friday
we're doing even more to this tattoo you
can see it's kind of bland there right
so we gotta we it's all the it's just
the faces right now we're filling it in
some more on friday but that's basically
the week
all right i literally feel like i need
to wear this too because i just came out
of the tanning slide
what the [__] is this wait oh god you
can't even see like
but it's so poofy oh man
[Laughter]
we're gonna go get the car cleaned up
here it's a little bit messy
i haven't cleaned it in months i haven't
been driving it too much so we gotta go
wash her
wash a little baby girl little baby boy
i should call him a boy just to piss
some
some of you guys off bro you can't call
your car a boy little charles
charles charles the green the green
[__] jig hey this british is a
british name charles that's why it's
charles all right whatever
barbara ash i don't know if you guys
remember mr bean
he lived with us for a little while he's
a big boy now hello
he's having a temper tantrum because he
can't go outside but look
finally i told you guys i was getting a
haircut now i just need to trim the
beard
and then we're good to go but coming
back uh real quick to start off the
stream
guys uh because five o'clock means
stream time every day asia open
all right it's nice and clean now
oh there we go
nice and clean
yeah let's do it i had to bounce out of
there real quick um
i tried to take a call busy lady i'm
and i am quite busy too so i have to
head home here should be good i gotta
shave this [__] beard too or i'm
gonna be
[__] flip-flopped around here now hey
all right boys it's been a couple weeks
since i recorded some of those clips and
my place is
absolutely trashed i just don't honestly
have any time
whatsoever to clean up anyways
we're talking about self-improvement
here in those past
clips there and i have been doing a
number of things
for just general sense of
self-improvement over the past couple
weeks
uh i have been getting outside doing
tons of activities i've actually decided
that i'm gonna start training for a
triathlon just these are things guys i
am so freaking impulsive with everything
anytime somebody says
they wanna do something i'm say yes i'm
gonna do it
uh they're not even asking me to do it
i'll do it on my own it's just
really it's like kind of that yes man
mentality
where you just don't have a whole lot of
life
so you gotta you gotta experience as
much as everything you can do as much
[__] as you can as quick as you can
gonna go buy a bike today so i can start
training for the triathlon these are
just challenges in your life guys if you
can challenge yourself
improve your discipline it's gonna help
you with the trading world too it's not
just you know your diet your exercise
and things like this
but i think it's very very underrated
it's the people you surround yourself
with
whenever there's somebody who's throwing
shade
that's kind of trying to bring you down
right that's their own insecurities
trying to make it so that they don't
have to work hard
themselves so that they can keep you at
their level when i've been around these
people
for example i told somebody about the
triathlon and they started making fun of
me they're like you can't do that right
and
i was like well that's the whole point
like i'm gonna be crap now that's why
i'm trying to improve so i can actually
do it as a challenge for myself
and then i realize this person's
terrible this person has no motivation
for their life anymore
so i don't want them in my life so i cut
them right and
that's what i've been doing anybody
who's throwing shade that's not
an uplifting positive person that's not
just there
to reinforce your improvement don't want
them in your life
and just doing that has made absolutely
remarkable
happiness changes i'm meeting great
brand new people
georgie stop eating the plant made me
start to think about this community and
i know
my channel there uh we've made a lot of
like making fun
of other forex youtubers right and it's
because
i think their strategies are crap and
they're just trying to they're just
trying to get the views
uh and they're not actually trying to
teach you anything they don't really
know much
and that's why we're kind of making fun
of them but i i realized i need i need a
gear shift
right and if i'm throwing shade like
that
then it's going to make me less happy
right even though
it's basically what i'm doing is when i
make fun of somebody it's
for jokes and then it gets more views
and so i'm basically doing the exact
same thing that i'm essentially making
fun of just in a different means
and so i'm probably going to be growing
at a slower rate
for not doing these uh you know funny
like making fun of type videos but i'm
going to try to be much more positive
i'm still going to make these videos
where i react to things but i want to
come across
in a very uplifting way and more helpful
and that's more for my own happiness and
hopefully
it kind of throws some light
and inspires some people as well to kind
of focus on just the positive things in
life
because it's it's absolutely unreal just
a couple weeks
completely focusing not drinking
freaking just
exercising sleeping eating perfectly has
in a couple weeks completely changed i
went from a completely depressed state
to um probably the happiest i've ever
been in my life
and so that's all i really wanted to say
about this video here guys
i mean let's jump into some sort of
charts or something for the week here so
that you guys can kind of see
what's going on now that's all i have to
say let's uh
best of luck everybody much love
[Music]
so
you